Guide to the Yale Law School Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Office of the Dean records, 1901-1961; Accession 1981-A-014
  - Subject and Correspondence Files, 1903-1961; Series III
    - Teas--Student and Faculty, 1935-1941 (Box 87, Folder 341)
    - Tennessee Bar and Examinations, 1932-1951 (Box 87, Folder 342)
    - Thomas Swan Barristers Union, 1935-1954 (Box 87, Folder 343)
    - Thorne, Samuel E., 1945-1957 (Box 87, Folder 344)
    - Throop, Allen E., 1937-1942 (Box 87, Folder 345)
    - Thurston, Edward S., 1919-1939 (Box 87, Folder 346)
    - Tighe, Z. G. (Treasurer's Office), 1941-1947 (Box 87, Folder 347)
    - Treasurer's Office, 1931-1948, 1951-1960 (Box 87, Folder 348-352)
    - Tugwell, Rexford G., 1933-1937 (Box 88, Folder 353)
    - Two-Way Fellowship, 1946-1954 (Box 88, Folder 354-359)
    - Undergraduate Curriculum, 1925-1941 (Box 88, Folder 360)
    - Vance, William R., 1920-1941 (Box 88, Folder 362)
    - Veterans' Administration, 1945-1951, 1950-1956 (Box 89, Folder 365-366, Box 88, Folder 362-364)
    - Visiting Sterling Lecturers, 1934-1943 (Box 89, Folder 368)
    - Wallace, Gerald L., 1933-1945 (Box 89, Folder 369)
    - War Service, 1940-1942 (Box 89, Folder 370)
    - Louis Weiss Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 89, Folder 371-372)
    - West Publishing Company, 1956-1960 (Box 89, Folder 373-374)
    - West Publishing Company, 1932-1956 (Box 90, Folder 375-378)
    - Wickser Philip J., 1931-1937 (Box 90, Folder 379)
    - Willkie for President Club, 1940 (Box 90, Folder 380)
    - Wisconsin Bar and Examinations, 1941-1949 (Box 90, Folder 381)
    - Work Sheets, Provost's Office, 1937-1942 (Box 90, Folder 382)
    - World Community and Law, 1956-1960 (Box 90, Folder 383)
    - Wynne, William H., 1934-1938 (Box 90, Folder 384)
    - Yale News, 1931-1957 (Box 90, Folder 385-387)
    - Yale Station Post Office, 1942-1949 (Box 90, Folder 388)
    - Yale University Press, 1936-1948, 1950-1956 (Box 90, Folder 389-390)
- Account book of Simeon E. Baldwin, 1874-1910; Accession 1983-A-026
  - Account book: Simeon E. Baldwin, treasurer in account with the Yale Law Library, 1874-1910 (Box 1)
- Letter to Carl A. Osterman, 1920; Accession 1991-A-123
  - Letter to Carl A. Osterman, 1920 January 9 (Box 1)
- Records concerning Professor Fred Rodell, 1939-1946; Accession 1992-A-047
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Records concerning Professor Fred Rodell, 1939-1946 (Box 1)